Guide to the Records of the Tisch School of the Arts 1956-1981 (Bulk 1965-1981) RG 35
New York University Archives
- Series II: David J. Oppenheim
  - Subseries A: Career at CBS; Oppenheim's general correnspondence while at CBS
    - Sub Subseries E: Reports and Conferences
      - Federal Communications Commission and Testimony of CBS, Oct 2, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Cleveland Conference on Public Service Programming, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Sub Subseries F: Promotional Material: "Play of the Week"
      - New Dramatist Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Play of the Week, Promotional, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Play of the Week, Promotional, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Play of the Week, Promotional, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Play of the Week, Promotional, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Sub Subseries G: Press Clippings, most of which are reviews of different Oppenheim broadcasts
      - CBS Storyline Summaries, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Reactions to Stravinsky, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: Research and Programming
    - Sub Subseries A: General Correspondence at PBL
      - Reviews, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Misc. PBL Notes and Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Interoffice Memos, the Living Theater, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Public Boradcastng, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Young Audiences Inc., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Misc. Notes and Memoes, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Misc. Correspondence, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Public Broadcastng, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Notes and Accounts, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Misc. Oppenheim, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Sub Subseries B: Research and Programming
      Included here is background information on a number of programs produced by Oppenheim, including his Jean-Luc Godard special, the broadcast about the Buffalo Arts Festival, and the Living Theatre.
      - PBL: Jazz Dance, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225793 4
      - PBL: Dance File, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Background on Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Ladislav Fialka--Czechoslovakia's Mime Theater, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - "Buffalo": Interviews at the Buffalo Arts Festival, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Jean Luc Godard Broadcast, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Notes and Correspondence: Jean Luc Godard, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Jean Luc Godard--Feature Film, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Programming: Poet Laureate, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Hubley-Hutchins: "Zuckerkandl", 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - "The Living Theater", 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Theater Announcements and Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - "Faces of War," and Other Programming, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Fred Bohen, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Misc. Programming, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Misc. Programming, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Misc. Programming, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Misc. Programming, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Sub Subseries C: Scripts and Transcripts
      - Frank Schwartz/"Love Lies Bleeding", undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Transcript from "Tango", 1968 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - "William Ball Show," #2, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Sub Subseries D: PBL Administration
      - National Education Television, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - PBL Financial Records and Receipts, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Early Career at NYU
    - Sub Subseries A: Early NYU Correspondence
      - Oppenheim: Beginnings at NYU, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - School of the Arts Memoes, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Sub Subseries B: Early NYU Administration
      - SOA Faculty Lists, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Proposal for MFA in Musical Theater, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Sub Subseries C: NYU Sesquicentennial
      - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225794 2
      - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Sesquicentennial Celebration and Other Misc. SOA Business, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Series III: Miscellaneous Reports
  - Broadcasting Foundation of America Report, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Frank J. Shakespeare Jr., V-P WCBS-TV, Keynote Address, American Women in Radio and Television, Inc., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, Reports and Bulletins, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Problems of Professional Playwrights, Report, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Inquiry: New York Legitimate Theatre, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Inquiry: New York Legitimate Theatre, undated (Box 8, Folder 10A)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Report, Dec 1963 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Institute of International Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Internation Education/Ford Foundation, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Institute of International Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Public Theater Funding Proposals, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Economic Forces in the African Theater, 1870-1967, Chapters 1-6, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Economic Forces in the African Theater, 1870-1967, Chapters 7-end, undated (Box 8, Folder 19A)
  - "The Negro and the Jew," by Dean Alex Rosen of the Graduate School of Social Work, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Donald Schoulty: Critical Writings, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Incomplete, Untitled Report, (annotated by Oppenheim), undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Incomplete Report: The Nonprofit Theater, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Incomplete, Unmarked Transcript, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Student Plays, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- ACCESSION 93-025
  - Series II: continued Oppenheim 1968-1974
    - Addresses (restricted), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225795 9
    - SOA Alumni Info, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Place Theatre, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Awards Scholarships, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Budget (restricted), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cinema Ph.D Program, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Conferences, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Dept. Cinema Studies, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - SOA Equipment Needs, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty (restricted), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Film History -Contemporary Cinema, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Film Library Contract, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - SOA Fundraising, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - GFTV, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of Drama, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Drama (Box 1, File 16A)
    - Drama and Cinema Program, Graduate Drama #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - UGFTV, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - UGFTV Student Affairs, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Intermedia, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - NYU Internal (removed to publications), 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Libraries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - David Oppenheim -Personal, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - NYC Projects, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Proposals, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225796 7
    - NYU Various Businesses, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - NYU Booklets, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Proposal For CBS Motion Picture Train., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Popular Cultural Program, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Early 70's Publicity, ca.1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cinema Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dance, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Design, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Drama, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - FTV, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Media Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - RAI -Radio Television Italiane, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - NYU Senate, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - SOA Various Businesses, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Student Affairs/Government, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Student Lists, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Student Plays, Scripts, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Subseries - Oppenheim, personal
      - David Oppenheim - Abe Friedman, Bernays, Eisner, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225797 5
      - David Oppenheim - Personal, Detroit Property, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - David Oppenheim - Detroit Property, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - David Oppenheim - Financial and Tax Records, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - David Oppenheim - Country House in South Hampton, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - David Oppenheim - Memoranda and Correspondence Originated by D.O.,Single Mailing, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - David Oppenheim - Memoranda and Correspondence Originated by D.O., Multiple Mailing, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - David Oppenheim - Passport, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - David Oppenheim - Personal Miscellaneous, Non-NYU Material, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - David Oppenheim - Personal "G", 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - David Oppenheim - Personal Information, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - David Oppenheim - Personal, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225798 3
      - David Oppenheim - Personal Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - David Oppenheim - Personal Insurance, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - David Oppenheim, Dean, 5-Year Evaluation of Deans, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - David Oppenheim, Separation Agreement Drafts 1-5, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        *removed
      - Stern, Isaac; Transcript, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Series IV: Development
    - Campaign Goals, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225799 1
    - Campaign Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Development -Foundations and Proposals For Funding, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Development - Grants and Scholarships, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Various Grants and Scholarships, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Development - Advisory Council SOA, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Development - California Trips, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Development- Film Production Fund, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225800 7
    - Development- NYU Office, Memos from Janet Grinell, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Projects, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Drama Review - Russian Theatre Project, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Proposal for Institute of Film and TV, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - NY State Council for the Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sponsored Research Monthly Report, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - A -D Alphabetical Miscellaneous, 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Subseries A: Development and 1968-1975, and Associate Dean Miller, 1969-1972
      - E-Z Alphabetical Miscellaneous, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225801 5
      - Dean Miller, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Academic Calendars, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Budget Salary Information, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence to dean Oppenheim, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence outside, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Richard Sawyer, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - State Educational Dept. Albany, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - National Endowment, Public Media, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Arts Reporting Service, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Heights Courses, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - American Dance Guild, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Dr. Fedenkrais Visit, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Faculty Appointment Information, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Blue Sheets, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Personnel Letters (1-40), (41-), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Dance Ensemble, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - J. Michael Miller Photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Recommendations, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Course Information Sheet, Instructions, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Course Information Sheets, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - National Endowment Proposal, 1968, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Building and Space, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Miller's Speech at Bennett College, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Commission on Undergraduate Education, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Budget Information, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04225802 3
      - Joe Zeigler, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Theatre Management Program, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Playwrights program, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Drama and Cinema, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Drama and Cinema Dept. Notes, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Boyd Compton-Mantra Intermedia, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Center for Arts of Indian America, Lee Udall, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - CBS Proposal, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Intermedia Graduate and Undergraduate, Film/TV, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Course Description, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence SOA, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Faculty Appointment Inquiries, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Expense account, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Course Information Sheet, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - School of Arts Ads, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Missing Equipment Report, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Financial Aid Material, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous Inter-University Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Faculty and Staff Information, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Series V: Administrative Files
    - Correspondence-Dean and Inter-University SOA, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225803 1
    - Curriculum, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Course Information Sheets, Spring 1972 Theatre Programs (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence Dean Oppenheim, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Outside University, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Paul Simon course, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget Sheets, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Augusto Boal, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Foundations, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Undegraduate Applicants, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Michael and the Boston Univ. Board of Visitors, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Michael -Bennett Summer Dance Program Evaluation, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kabuki, Onoe Kmoemon, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Government Grants, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Film Department Course List ,(Description of Courses, Studies in Communication), 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dance, (School, Studies Relationship), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Perception, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Perception Course, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - School of the Arts, (Schedules, Curriculum), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - End of the Year Reports, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - BFA Degree in Film and Television Description, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Inter-Arts Program Proposal, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - J. Michael Miller- Speeches- Fall 1970, August 1972, 1970, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - New Course Descriptions and Schedules, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225804 9
    - Ruth Mayleas, (Director, Theatre Programs, National Endowment for the Arts), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sabbatical Project, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Tenure Documents, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Section #10 NY State Arts Council, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - London Company Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Kezban's Curriculum, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Playwriting needs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Asia Society idea, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - National Scholarship Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - SOA Original Self-study; Status Report on the Theatre Program, Fall 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Arts Management, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - List of all NYU GSAS Grads, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1973-74 Correspondence Outside NYU, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1973-74 Memos From Dean Oppenheim, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1973-74 Correspondence within SOA, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1973-74 Correspondence within NYU, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1973-74 Memos to Dean Oppenheim, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1973-74 Incoming Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 1973-74 Management file, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Christodoulakis, George, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Business Committee on the Arts, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Janet Grinnell, SOA Funding Possibilities, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - New Dept.of Performing Arts-J.Oliva Memo, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Perception -Peter Phillips Fall, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Onoe Kuroemon, Kabuki Acting Center, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - J. Michael Miller, Curriculum Vitae for Sabbatical Leave Application, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - The National Ensowment for the Arts, Ruth Mayleas, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, Norman Lloyd, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Pop Culture, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - News Releases, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Film -Mailing Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Summer Session, Promotional Material, Adds, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Summer Session, Bulletin, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225805 6
    - Contacts, I, II Peter Moore Photos, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Summer Session, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Outside NYU, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - David Oppenheim, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - SOA, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Incoming, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Within NYU, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Biog. Material, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - NYSCA, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Budget Sheets, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Dance Critics Mailing List, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Selma Jean Cohen, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Commission on Cultural Resources, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Letters, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Admissions, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225806 4
    - Ambery, George: Cinema Studies, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Arts Administration GPA, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Awards and Fundraising, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Communication Arts Group, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Conferences, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Equipment Needs and Description, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Faculty, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Financial Aid, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Goggin, Richard, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Intermedia, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - International Arts Program, Center for International Studies, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Film and TV, Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Levinson, Al: Theatre Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Institute of Performing Arts, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Libraries, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Lippman, Monroe: Cinema Studies, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Miller, Michael: Director Theatre Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - National Council of Fine Arts Deans, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Gifts, 1970, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225807 2
    - Gifts and Pledges, 1970-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Progress Reports, 1970, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - NYU Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Physical Plant, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Public Occasions, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Proposals, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Saudek, Robert: Institut of Film and TV, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Schechner, Richard: Editor, Drama Review, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - School of the Arts, Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sterling Forest Summer Theatre, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Student Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Student Housing, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Student Lists, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - TMR Department, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - General Policy, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Theatre Administration Center, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - WNYU, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Theatre Program, Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Financial Aid -Martin Luther King Grant, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225808 0
    - SOA NYU General, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SOA Theatre Curriculum, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SOA Annual Reports, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - UG/Grad Theatre Prgms., undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Admissions, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Policies-Legal, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - SOA Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - General Programs- Drama/Theatre, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Committees, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Policies-Committees for SOA/NYU, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Cinema Graduate Programs, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Institutional Services Office,1969, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Resumes/Bibliographies, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Services, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Purchasing, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Office of Research. Services, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Research/Grant Proposal, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Student Council, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - SOA Banner Shields/Design, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Printed Materials, NYU and miscellaneous, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Robert Sauder/Confidential, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225809 8
    - Manhattan Cable, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - GFTV - Programs, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Student Films, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Student/Faculty Memos, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Curriculum, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Leasing List, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Theatre Budget, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Capital Budget Requests, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - NYU General Documents, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - PBL, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - SOA Calendar, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Administration, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Compton, Boyd - Intermedia, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - SOA Library Material, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - SOA Council Proposal, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Resolution, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Students, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - UGFTV, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - CBS/DO Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Equipment Problems, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Saplin-Stanley, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Faculty, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Budget, Students & Tuition, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Budget Comparison, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Budgets: Deans Office Codes Building DO Notes Miscellaneous Intermedia Drama/Upman SOA Programs Inst. FTV, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Rules of Faculty Council/Senate, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)